[{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":10254,"timeElapsed":188170},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980329432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7143,"timeElapsed":195314},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980333032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3599,"timeElapsed":198914},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980339840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6807,"timeElapsed":205722},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980345880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6039,"timeElapsed":211762},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980350496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4614,"timeElapsed":216378},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980358016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7519,"timeElapsed":223898},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8567,"timeElapsed":232465},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"51","question":"Do you think people can change fundamental things about who they are? If so, what kinds of things? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3351,"timeElapsed":235817},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980378855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7711,"timeElapsed":244737},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1759,"timeElapsed":246497},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2311,"timeElapsed":248809},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1999,"timeElapsed":250809},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1263,"timeElapsed":252073},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980388367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2175,"timeElapsed":254249},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980389775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1407,"timeElapsed":255657},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980391263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1487,"timeElapsed":257145},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980392431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1167,"timeElapsed":258313},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":6519,"timeElapsed":265657},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1463,"timeElapsed":267121},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980402631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1391,"timeElapsed":268513},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3095,"timeElapsed":271609},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1016,"timeElapsed":272625},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":942,"timeElapsed":273569},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4023,"timeElapsed":277593},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1071,"timeElapsed":278665},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":951,"timeElapsed":279616},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980418383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3783,"timeElapsed":284265},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1391,"timeElapsed":285657},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1535,"timeElapsed":287192},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":289736},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2175,"timeElapsed":291912},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980428391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2359,"timeElapsed":294273},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1663,"timeElapsed":295936},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2079,"timeElapsed":298016},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1415,"timeElapsed":299432},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3367,"timeElapsed":303672},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":305712},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":308432},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":5591,"timeElapsed":314024},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2423,"timeElapsed":316448},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980452118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1551,"timeElapsed":318000},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980453838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1719,"timeElapsed":319720},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980455630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1791,"timeElapsed":321512},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1128,"timeElapsed":322640},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5278,"timeElapsed":328896},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1727,"timeElapsed":330624},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":333016},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980472998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5863,"timeElapsed":338880},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1823,"timeElapsed":340704},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478862,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4040,"timeElapsed":344744},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4302,"timeElapsed":349048},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1295,"timeElapsed":350343},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1839,"timeElapsed":352183},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980487486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1183,"timeElapsed":353368},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":7199,"timeElapsed":361608},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":363848},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1295,"timeElapsed":365143},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1984,"timeElapsed":367128},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1063,"timeElapsed":368191},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":1199,"timeElapsed":369391},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":1127,"timeElapsed":370519},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1135,"timeElapsed":371655},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980506861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1087,"timeElapsed":372743},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3823,"timeElapsed":377687},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2943,"timeElapsed":380631},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1543,"timeElapsed":382175},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1456,"timeElapsed":383632},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":975,"timeElapsed":384607},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980521141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":387023},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1223,"timeElapsed":388247},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1047,"timeElapsed":389295},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530605,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7191,"timeElapsed":396487},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3631,"timeElapsed":400119},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980540533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4959,"timeElapsed":406415},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2295,"timeElapsed":408711},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2063,"timeElapsed":410775},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2856,"timeElapsed":413631},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980549589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1838,"timeElapsed":415471},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3039,"timeElapsed":418511},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":420751},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1887,"timeElapsed":422639},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557948,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1191,"timeElapsed":423830},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":428038},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1839,"timeElapsed":429878},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2479,"timeElapsed":432358},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":434958},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1479,"timeElapsed":436438},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980573724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3167,"timeElapsed":439606},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1271,"timeElapsed":440878},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4031,"timeElapsed":444910},{"subjectID":"sofp2jb0vh","prolificID":"66d7586af25d8f19f78fe62a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b21f5a18c7727463dfa1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980580292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1263,"timeElapsed":446174}]